export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Акмурат Ходжатов",
    variants: ["Akmurat Khodzhatov", "Akmurat Hodzhatov", "Akmurat Khojatov"],
    answer: "Akmurat Khodzhatov",
  },
  {
    question: "Александр Ходыкин",
    variants: ["Aleksandr Hodykin", "Aleksandr Khodykin", "Alexander Khodykin"],
    answer: "Aleksandr Khodykin",
  },
  {
    question: "Александр Поляков",
    variants: ["Aleksandr Polyakov", "Alexander Polyakov"],
    answer: "Alexander Polyakov",
  },
  {
    question: "Александр Жидовленко",
    variants: ["Aleksandr Zhidovlenko", "Alexander Zhidovlenko"],
    answer: "Alexander Zhidovlenko",
  },
  {
    question: "Александр Зуев",
    variants: ["Aleksandr Zuev", "Alexander Zuev"],
    answer: "Alexander Zuev",
  },
  {
    question: "Александр Артюхов",
    variants: [
      "Aleksandr Artyuhov",
      "Alexandr Artyukhov",
      "Alexander Artyukhov",
    ],
    answer: "Alexandr Artyukhov",
  },
  {
    question: "Александр Леонов",
    variants: ["Alexander Leonov", "Aleksandr Leonov", "Alexandr Leonov"],
    answer: "Alexandr Leonov",
  },
  {
    question: "Александр Вежлев",
    variants: ["Aleksandr Vezhlev", "Alexander Vezhlev", "Alexandr Vezhlev"],
    answer: "Alexandr Vezhlev",
  },
  {
    question: "Амаль Абдуллаев",
    variants: ["Amal Abdullaev", "Akmal Abdullayev", "Amal Abdullayev"],
    answer: "Amal Abdullaev",
  },
  {
    question: "Антон Машошин",
    variants: ["Anton Mashoshin", "Anton Masoshin", "Anton Mashosin"],
    answer: "Anton Mashoshin",
  },
  {
    question: "Дарья Голубева",
    variants: ["Daria Golubeva", "Darya Golubeva"],
    answer: "Darya Golubeva",
  },
  {
    question: "Денис Хрипков",
    variants: ["Denis Hripkov", "Denis Khripkov"],
    answer: "Denis Khripkov",
  },
  {
    question: "Дима Нгуен",
    variants: ["Dima Nguyen", "Dmitriy Nguyen", "Dima Nguen"],
    answer: "Dmitriy Nguyen",
  },
  {
    question: "Дмитрий Данилов",
    variants: ["Dmitry Danilov", "Dmitrij Danilov"],
    answer: "Dmitry Danilov",
  },
  {
    question: "Дмитрий Гадеев",
    variants: ["Dmitrij Gadeev", "Dmitry Gadeev", "Dmitriy Gadeev"],
    answer: "Dmitry Gadeev",
  },
  {
    question: "Егор Ней",
    variants: ["Yegor Ney", "Egor Ney", "Egor Nej"],
    answer: "Egor Ney",
  },
  {
    question: "Егор Половинкин",
    variants: ["Egor Polovinkin", "Igor Polovinkin", "Polovinkin Egor"],
    answer: "Egor Polovinkin",
  },
  {
    question: "Игорь Буруля",
    variants: ["Igor Burbulya", "Igor Burulya"],
    answer: "Igor Burulya",
  },
  {
    question: "Игорь Дизгинжили",
    variants: ["Igor Dizginzhili", "Igor Dizginjili"],
    answer: "Igor Dizginzhili",
  },
  {
    question: "Иван Брякунов",
    variants: ["Ivan Bryakunov", "Bryakunov Ivan"],
    answer: "Ivan Bryakunov",
  },
  {
    question: "Кирилл Столяров",
    variants: ["Kirill Stolyarov", "Stolyarov Kirill"],
    answer: "Kirill Stolyarov",
  },
  {
    question: "Константин Грушин",
    variants: ["Konstantin Grushin", "Konstantin Grusin"],
    answer: "Konstantin Grushin",
  },
  {
    question: "Максим Алехнович",
    variants: ["Maxim Alekhnovich", "Maksim Alekhnovich", "Maksim Alehnovich"],
    answer: "Maksim Alekhnovich",
  },
  {
    question: "Максим Чернухин",
    variants: ["Maxim Chernukhin", "Maksim Chernukhin", "Maksim Chernuhin"],
    answer: "Maksim Chernukhin",
  },
  {
    question: "Марина Алексюк",
    variants: ["Marina Aleksyuk", "Marina Alexiuk"],
    answer: "Marina Aleksyuk",
  },
  {
    question: "Михаил Авдеев",
    variants: ["Mihail Avdeev", "Mikhail Avdeev"],
    answer: "Mikhail Avdeev",
  },
  {
    question: "Михаил Сороколет",
    variants: ["Mihail Sorokolet", "Mikhail Sorokolet", "Mikhail Sorokoletov"],
    answer: "Mikhail Sorokolet",
  },
  {
    question: "Наталия Шпер",
    variants: ["Natalia Shper", "Nataliya Shper"],
    answer: "Natalia Shper",
  },
  {
    question: "Николай Лаевский",
    variants: [
      "Nikolaj Laevskij",
      "Nikolai Laevskii",
      "Nikolay Laevsky",
      "Nikolai Laevsky",
    ],
    answer: "Nikolai Laevskii",
  },
  {
    question: "Николай Шубин",
    variants: ["Nikolai Shubin", "Nikolay Shubin", "Nikolaj Shubin"],
    answer: "Nikolay Shubin",
  },
  {
    question: "Никита Нафранец",
    variants: ["Nikita Nafranets", "Nikita Nafranec"],
    answer: "Nikita Nafranets",
  },
  {
    question: "Олег Кузняк",
    variants: ["Oleg Kuznyak", "Oleg Kuzniak"],
    answer: "Oleg Kuznyak",
  },
  {
    question: "Олег Морозов",
    variants: ["Oleg Morozov"],
    answer: "Oleg Morozov",
  },
  {
    question: "Ольга Копьева",
    variants: ["Olga Kopyeva", "Olga Kopjeva", "Olga Kopeva"],
    answer: "Olga Kopyeva",
  },
  {
    question: "Павел Андреев",
    variants: ["Pavel Andreev", "Pavel Andreiv"],
    answer: "Pavel Andreev",
  },
  {
    question: "Паша Старовойтов",
    variants: ["Pasha Starovoitov", "Pasha Starovojtov", "Pavel Starovoytov"],
    answer: "Pavel Starovoytov",
  },
  {
    question: "Роман Гранков",
    variants: ["Roman Croutons", "Roman Grankov"],
    answer: "Roman Grankov",
  },
  {
    question: "Роман Новожилов",
    variants: ["Roman Novozhilov"],
    answer: "Roman Novozhilov",
  },
  {
    question: "Сергей Пеняев",
    variants: [
      "Penyaev Sergey",
      "Sergej Penyaev",
      "Sergei Penyaev",
      "Sergey Penyaev",
    ],
    answer: "Penyaev Sergey",
  },
  {
    question: "Сергей Сахаровский",
    variants: [
      "Sergei Sakharovskii",
      "Sergej Saharovskij",
      "Sergey Sakharovsky",
      "Sergei Sakharovsky",
    ],
    answer: "Sergei Sakharovskii",
  },
  {
    question: "Степан Быстрай",
    variants: ["Stepan Bystray", "Stepan Bystraj", "Stepan Bystry"],
    answer: "Stepan Bystray",
  },
  {
    question: "Владислав Перетягин",
    variants: ["Vlad Peretyagin", "Vladislav Peretyagin"],
    answer: "Vlad Peretyagin",
  },
  {
    question: "Всеволод Андрущенко",
    variants: [
      "Vsevolod Andryushchenko",
      "Vsevolod Andrushenko",
      "Vsevolod Andruschenko",
      "Vsevolod Andrushchenko",
    ],
    answer: "Vsevolod Andruschenko",
  },
  {
    question: "Ян Павленко",
    variants: ["Yan Pavlenko", "Yann Pavlenko", "Jan Pavlenko"],
    answer: "Yann Pavlenko",
  },
  {
    question: "Ян Парфенов",
    variants: ["Yan Parfenov", "Jan Parfenov"],
    answer: "Yan Parfenov",
  },
];

export default function handler(req, res) {
  res.status(200).json(questions.map(({ answer, ...question }) => question));
}
